exports.trivia = {
    0:{question:"What was the championship skin that was released for the Season 2 World Championships?",answer:"Championship Riven"},
    1:{question:"What item hides a famous cliche inside one of it's values?",answer:"Brutalizer"},
    2:{question:"What Super Smash Bros. Melee character was Riven modeled after?",answer:"Marth"},
    3:{question:"Who was one of the first champions designed in League of Legends?",answer:"Singed"},
    4:{question:"What instrument does High Noon Yasuo play in his dance animation?",answer:"Harmonica"},
    5:{question:"Who was the first Manaless champ to have a 100 difficulty rating?",answer:"Rumble"},
    6:{question:"What famous martial arist is the skin Dragonfist Lee Sin based off of?",answer:"Bruce Lee"},
    7:{question:"Who was the first champ to use energy that is not a ninja?",answer:"Lee Sin"},
    8:{question:"Which champion has a dance and skin based off of the popular J-Pop group Girls Generation?",answer:"Ahri"},
    9:{question:"Which champion's wife's soul did Thresh trap in his lantern?",answer:"Lucian"},
    10:{question:"Which champion is described to have a \"Global Taunt\"?",answer:"Teemo"},
    11:{question:"Which champion is Darius's younger brother?",answer:"Draven"},
    12:{question:"What AP Caster has more attack range than most ADCs?",answer:"Annie"},
    13:{question:"Which champ is the only one to say the word \"noob\"?",answer:"Akali"},
    14:{question:"Which champion has a dance based off of one found in the show South ParK?",answer:"Amumu"},
    15:{question:"Which champion's ultimate features varius sad face emoticons?",answer:"Amumu"},
    16:{question:"Which champion is Amumu's only friend?",answer:"Annie"},
    17:{question:"What is the name of the ancient queen that Ashe's bow once belonged to?",answer:"Avarosa"},
    18:{question:"Which champions was the first to have a full rework of their splash arts?",answer:"Ashe"},
    19:{question:"Which champion was the first to feature a unique attack animation for attacking turrets?",answer:"Braum"},
    20:{question:"What champ other than Nami says words in their Laugh animation?",answer:"Fiddlesticks"},
    21:{question:"What is the name of the iconic manatee in League of Legends?",answer:"Urf"},
};
